Kaden Eldridge-Edwards

(214) 842-7854 - Eldridgekadenedwards@gmail.com -Rowlett, Tx - LinkedIn

Achiever - Analytical - Focus - Restorative - Responsibility

Summary

I aim to grow my knowledge of the Information Technology ecosystem. My current skills and experience in programming and troubleshooting, as well as my experience building and configuring both PCs and servers, will help me to further understand and excel at tasks as a Tech Process Associate.

Experience

August 2020 to May 2021

RMSI Retail Merchadising Solutions Inc, Dallas, TX - Merchandiser - Team Lead Backup

- Improve methods of operation to reduce total minutes per set.
- Document issues within stores to maintain accurate details for proper changes to occur.
- Produce updated store maps for future reference within the company.
- Mobilize a group of Merchandisers to complete store visits while Team Lead(s) attend wave meetings.

August 2017 to July 2019

Edible Arrangements, Rockwall, TX - Manager

- Monitor food preparation methods, portion sizes, garnishing, and presentation of food to ensure that food is prepared and presented in an acceptable manner.
- Investigate and resolve complaints regarding food quality, service, or accommodations.
- Schedule and receive product deliveries, checking delivery contents to verify product quality and quantity.
- Schedule staff hours and assign duties.

Skills

Coding (Java, Python, CSS, HTML, C++), Troubleshooting, Type 1 Hypervisor Management, System Configuration

Education & Certification

September 2021 to November 2021

New Apprenticeship

May 2021 - Present

Code Academy - Full Stack Engineer path

May 2021 - June 2021

Coursera - Technical Support Fundamentals by Google

May 2021

Code Academy - Code Foundation Certificate

May 2021

Code Academy - Learn To Code Certificate

August 2016 to June 2019

Rowlett High School - High school diploma